[
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "verb: volver",
		"back": "to return, to go back; irregular; o>ue; pres: vuelvo, vuelves, vuelve, vuelven; pastpart: vuelto",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 09:19:03"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "I may come back",
		"back": "tal vez pueda volver",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 09:18:14"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "I unfolded the map on the desk",
		"back": "desplegué el mapa sobre el escritorio",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 09:12:26"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "verb: desplegar",
		"back": "to deploy, to spred out; irregular; e>ie, gé>gué; pres: despliego, despliegas, despliega, despliegan; pret: desplegué",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 09:08:35"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "we've got to stick to the facts",
		"back": "tenemos que ceñirnos a los hechos",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 08:57:16"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "verb: ceñir",
		"back": "to stick to something; e>i; irregular; pres: ciño, ciñes, ciñe, ciñen; pret: ciñó, ciñieron",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 08:45:08"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "I'll stick to my original plan",
		"back": "me ceñiré a mi plan original",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 08:46:42"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "you all see here that",
		"back": "así veis que",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:56:32"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "every time you all see",
		"back": "cada vez que veáis",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:59:02"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "I want you to see this",
		"back": "quiero que veas esto",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 03:00:18"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "I want you all to see this",
		"back": "quiero que veáis esto",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 03:00:18"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "they can be used",
		"back": "se pueden utilizar",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:53:11"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "depending on performance",
		"back": "dependiendo del rendimiento",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:47:42"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "he sticks to his principles",
		"back": "él se ciñe a sus principios",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:40:26"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "he sticks with his own theory",
		"back": "él se ciñe a su propia teoría",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 02:40:43"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "complete waste of resources",
		"back": "total derroche de recursos",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 20:57:56"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "PR.vallarlas",
		"back": "bar-JAR-lass - to fence them in",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 21:14:01"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "are usually optimized (tend to be optimized)",
		"back": "suelen estar optimizados",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 21:14:03"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "reducing spending",
		"back": "reduciendo el gasto",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 21:17:31"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "we can go see",
		"back": "podemos ir viendo",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 23:10:51"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "deployments",
		"back": "despliegues",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-09 23:14:19"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "the matter is limited to two",
		"back": "el asunto se ciñe a dos",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 00:08:25"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "if there is no error",
		"back": "si no hay fallo",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 00:16:32"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "the cost amounted to twelve pesos",
		"back": "el gasto llegó a doce pesos",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 00:54:55"
	},
	{
		"category": "spanish",
		"front": "what a waste of energy",
		"back": "qué gasto de energía",
		"learned": false,
		"timesTested": 0,
		"whenLastTested": "",
		"whenCreated": "2022-09-10 00:45:55"
	}
]
